BGM
Good morning.
I am on the annual summer FC tour.
I wanted to do something summery and easy to understand.
The dress code was “Yukata Live” for all the guests.
Customers in yukata, too.
The audience is also in yukata?
It's a dress code.
It's like a yukata dress.
Something that shows off the legs.
It's easy to dance in.
If I make a yukata with a ready-made pattern
I think it's too cheesy.
Wouldn't it be better to draw the pattern yourself?
You can draw the pattern yourself.
I think so.
I think it's better to make it.
You can do that.
I was thinking of putting the G logo on it.
I was thinking of doing that on my own.
But I thought it would be impossible.
You can do it.
Okay, then.
I'll tell you what.
I'd like to buy the customers' favorite snacks.
I'd like to serve them.
I'm looking forward to it.
Laughs.
Good morning.
Congratulations
Congratulations!
It's so cute.
Thank you
He's so cute.
Amazing.
Beautiful.
So cute. Cute.
Really?
I'm so happy.
I want to wear it.
Thank you so much.
That's amazing.
You're crazy.
Isn't your makeup so good?
I'm curious.
Yukata (Japanese bathrobe)
Thank you.
Cute.
It's cute.
I can wear panes inside and stuff.
So is the bag.
Isn't it amazing? Original fabric.
It's original fabric.
There's some kind of fabric in there.
I don't know.
That's right.
It's amazing.
Young Parade
Oh, my gosh!
They're so cute.
They could all be yellow.
All yellow?
It's red fabric.
It's the yellow one.
Wait a minute.
When you get back.
He's so cute.
And, and, and...
Eh, gal.
Super cute!
We matched her nails too.
Gal's mom dressed her. The gal's mom dressed her.
kid gal
tall
I knew she was big!
She's tall!
I have this.
I wonder if I can sell it.
I'll take it.
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm in the Heisei era.
But you're right.
The ceiling is close.
Please, please, please.
I'll go.
You look like a gal.
Thank you very much.
Cute.
Is it okay?
Thank you very much.
You know, the other day, when I got it for the first time...
The cloth you designed?
Cloth?
I designed a pattern for a costume.
I thought it was really cute.
I thought it was really cute, but I hadn't worn it at that time.
I thought it would look great in a hair ornament
I also wanted to make it more voluminous
more like a yukata dress.
I'm feeling really excited about it. I'm feeling a tremendous upsurge.
What if we decide to continue to be a “gal” in the future?
It's not so much that I'm going to be a gal.
We do the FC tour every summer.
I wanted to go out and do something summery.
I thought about what I wanted to do, and I thought of a festival.
I thought it would be nice to go and have a festival.
I thought it would be nice.
Then we decided to use yukata as the dress code.
When I thought about what kind of yukata I should wear
I'd never worn a yukata dress before.
When I was a little older
I remembered that I had wanted to try it once when I was a little older.
I thought this would be the only chance to wear such a dress.
I thought that a yukata dress would suit a slightly girly look.
I did some research and found that
I found that most of the yukata wearers were kids who looked like “gyaru”.
I found that most of them were kids who looked like gyaru.
So I decided to go with that look.
I talked with the makeup artist today.
I'm going to use light blue eyeshadow to make it look a little more gyaru.
I want to be educated as a convicted gyaru.
Fingernails, too.
There's not much fabric left.
I was told to design them myself.
I came up with my own.
This one says “Gang Parade” on it.
It's not the same as “Gang Parade” but it's in capital letters.
It's hard to tell at first glance.
Actually, I thought the name “Gang Parade” is a little bit like “Gyaru-chan”.
I thought it looks a little bit like a “gyaru” (gal) with the letters.
It's got chains and stuff.
The hair ornament is really cute.
I don't think there are usually hair ornaments in Gang Parade costumes.
I don't think there are usually hair ornaments in the parade costumes.
So you can see such a rare hair ornament.
Before I had the hair ornament made
I was sure that my own hair ornament would be better.I thought for sure I was better than this.
I got it like this and tried it on.
And then, when I looked at the others who were fitting at the same time, I realized that
I saw that other people's clothes looked really good, too.
Like SEI's.
SEI's is a donut, but I don't know what the other members will be like.
I don't know what will happen to the other members.
But there are members from all over the world.
I wonder what will happen if 13 members come.
I'm curious to see what will happen when the 13 members come.
Let's have a great summer with us!
I'm looking forward to working with you!